Guide to the Frank Lyon Polk Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Correspondence, 1898-(1915-1920)-1942; Series I; 6.5 linear feet (16 boxes)
  - Bristol, Mark L., 1919 October - 1920 Aug; 1921 June, Nov; 1929 June (Box 3, Folder 71-73)
  - Broderick, John Joyce, 1917 June - 1918 February (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Brooklyn Times, 1915 December (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Brooks, Sydney, 1915 Feb, 1917 June - December (Box 3, Folder 75)
    See also: Cuba, box 24, folder 207
  - Brougham, Herbert Bruce, 1916 January - 1917 October (Box 3, Folder 75)
    See also: William C. Bullitt (1917 Oct 24), box 3, folder 89
  - Brown, James Crosby, 1919 January - February (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Brown, Lucius Polk, 1918 December - 1919 January (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Brown, Samuel A., 1918 September (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Brown Brothers and Company
    See: Lucius Hart Beers, box 2, folder 44 See: James Crosby Brown, box 3, folder 76
  - Bruère, Henry
    - (*), 1916 July - 1917 April (Box 3, Folder 77-78)
    - (*), 1917 May - October (Box 3, Folder 79)
      See also: Julian B. Beaty (1917 Jun 4), box 2, folder 43
    - 1917 November 2-15 (Box 3, Folder 80)
    - (*), 1917 November 16 - 1918 June (Box 3, Folder 81-82)
    - 1918 August - December (Box 3, Folder 83)
    - (*), 1919 January - Jun, 1920 January, 1931 January (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - (*) Brun, Constantin, 1915 Dec, 1916 Aug, 1917 July - Aug, 1918 May - Dec, 1920 June (Box 3, Folder 85-86)
  - Bryant, Louise, 1918 June - July (Box 3, Folder 87)
  - Bryce, James, 1st viscount of Dechmont, Lanarkshire, 1919 August (Box 3, Folder 87)
    See also: James David Bourchier, box 2, folder 67
  - Bryn, H. H., 1918 December (Box 3, Folder 87)
  - Buckler, William Hepburn, 1919 December - 1920 March (Box 3, Folder 88)
    See also: Georgia, box 25, folder 264 See also: Near East, box 31, folder 552 See also: Turkey, box 36, folders 824-828
  - Bull, Henry W., 1916 January - February (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - Bullard, Arthur
    See: George Creel (1918 Feb 26), box 4, folders 128-129
  - Bullitt, William C., 1916 Sep, 1917 Oct, 1918 January (Box 3, Folder 89)
    See also: Labor, box 28, folder 409 See also: Russia, box 33, folder 675
  - Bumçi, Louis, 1919 August (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - Bureau of Municipal Research, 1911 June (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - Burke, Thomas F., 1916 March (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - Burleson, Albert Sidney, 1916 January - Feb, Oct; 1924 July (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - Burlingham, Charles C., 1916 January - February (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - Burnside, R. H., 1918 December - 1919 Jan, 1924 July (Box 3, Folder 91)
  - Business Training Corporation, 1916 July - November (Box 3, Folder 91)
  - Butler, Wyckoff and Campbell, 1920 March (Box 3, Folder 91)
  - Buxton, Noel, 1919 August (Box 3, Folder 92)
    See also: Rumania, box 32, folder 644
  - Byrne, Helen MacGregor (Mrs. James), 1919 March - April (Box 3, Folder 92)
  - Byrne, James, 1919 March (Box 3, Folder 92)
  - Cabrera, Luis
    See: Henry Bruére, box 3, folders 77-78, 1917 Apr 20 See: Charles A. Douglas, box 5, folder 151
  - Caffey, Francis Gordon, 1917 Sep, 1920 May (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - Calder, William M., 1917 Sep, 1919 March (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - Caldwell, Charles Pope, 1916 September (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - Caldwell, John L.
    See: Persia, box 32, folder 602
  - Canova, Leon Joseph
    See: American Red Cross, box 1, folder 5 See: Norman Hapgood (1916 Sep 11), box 7, folder 231 See: Mexico, box 28, folders 443-488
  - [Cantacuzène, Julia Grant Speransky?], 1919 July - August (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - Cardashian, Vahan, 1919 December - 1920 March (Box 3, Folder 94)
    See also: Gardiner Howland Shaw, box 12, folder 430
  - Carew, John F., 1919 March (Box 3, Folder 94)
  - (*) Carey, Francis King, 1919 December - 1920 February (Box 3, Folder 95)
  - Carlin, Charles Creighton, 1919 September (Box 3, Folder 95)
  - Carlton, Newcomb, 1917 August (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - Carnegie, Thomas Morrison, 1918 November (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - Carpatho-Russian Committee
    See also: Poland, box 32, folder 624
  - Carr, Wilbur J., 1920 June - November (Box 3, Folder 97)
    See also: Canada, box 24, folder 183 See also: State Department, box 34, folder 764
  - Carroll, Charles, 1915 September (Box 3, Folder 97)
    See also: Fred Hoey, box 8, folder 260
  - Carroll, Thomas J.
    See: Peter Brady, box 2, folder 69
  - Carteron, ____, 1919 August - September (Box 3, Folder 97)
  - (*) Cartier de Marchienne, Emile de, 1918 December - 1920 December; 1921 December; 1924 May, December; 1925 Apr; 1926 Apr; 1927 June; 1928 Jan; 1940 June (Box 3, Folder 98)
  - Cassavetes, Nicholas J., 1920 January - June (Box 3, Folder 99)
  - Castle, William Richards, Jr., 1927 February, 1928 February - March (Box 3, Folder 99)
  - Cecil, Edgar Algernon Robert Gascoyne-Cecil, viscount
    See: Frederic R. Coudert (1917 Jun 7), box 4, folders 118-119
  - (*) Cellere, Vincenzo Macchi di, 1916 February - 1918 October (Box 3, Folder 100-101)
  - Cespedes, Carlos Manuel de, 1919 November (Box 3, Folder 102)
  - Chabot, Frederic C., 1918 October - 1919 May (Box 3, Folder 102)
  - Chadbourne, Thomas L., 1919 February (Box 3, Folder 102)
  - Chambliss, William Henry
    See: Wilbur J. Carr, box 3, folder 97
  - Chambrun, Louis Charles de, count
    See: China, box 24, folder 195
  - Chandler, Percy M., 1917 March, Oct; 1918 March (Box 3, Folder 103)
  - Cheney, S. A., 1919 December (Box 3, Folder 103)
    See also: Baltic States, box 23, folder 146
  - Childers, Henry H., 1919 January (Box 3, Folder 104)
  - Chinda, Sutemi, 1916 Feb, July (Box 3, Folder 104)
  - Churchill, Marlborough, 1919 July - November, 1928 November (Box 3, Folder 105)
  - Churchill, Thomas William, 1919 February - March (Box 3, Folder 105)
  - Civil Service Chronicle, 1916 November (Box 3, Folder 105)
  - Clark, Benjamin Preston, 1915 November (Box 3, Folder 106)
  - Clark, Charles A., 1921 December (Box 3, Folder 106)
  - Clark, Charles Upson, 1919 October - 1920 June (Box 3, Folder 106)
  - Clarke, Samuel B.
    See: Francis Gordon Caffey, box 3, folder 93
  - Clemenceau, Georges, 1919 August - Dec, 1920 October (Box 3, Folder 107)
    See also: Adriatic Question, box 21, folder 18 See also: Adriatic Question, box 21, folder 35
  - Clerk, George Russell, 1919 September - December (Box 3, Folder 108)
    See also: Harry Hill Bandholtz, box 2, folder 38 See also: Rumania, box 32, folder 654
  - Cléry, Cochin de, 1919 September (Box 3, Folder 108)
  - (*) Cobb, Zach Lamar, 1916 October - 1918 December (Box 3, Folder 108)
  - Cobbs, T. D., 1920 January - February (Box 4, Folder 109)
  - Cochran, Gifford A., 1918 January - February (Box 4, Folder 109)
  - Coggill, George, 1916 August (Box 4, Folder 109)
  - Cogswell, George E., 1919 March - April (Box 4, Folder 109)
  - Coit, James Milnor
  - Colby, Bainbridge, 1917 Mar, Oct; 1919 December (Box 4, Folder 110)
  - Coleman, Thomas J.
    See: Mexico, box 30, folder 511
  - Collier, Robert J., 1913 Apr; 1916 Jul, October (Box 4, Folder 110)
  - Columbia Trust Company, 1919 June (Box 4, Folder 110)
  - Commercial Cable Company
    See: Clarence H. Mackay, box 10, folders 339-342
  - Compania de Minerales y Metales
    See: Julian B. Beaty, box 2, folder 43 See: Henry Bruére (1916 Dec 18), box 3, folders 77-78
  - Continental Petroleum Company
    See: Guy Stevens, box 12, folder 447
  - Coolidge, Archibald Cary
    See: Albania, box 22, folder 93 See: Greece, box 26, folder 341
  - Cosgrave, John O'Hara, 1917 October (Box 4, Folder 111)
  - Cottenet, Rawlins Lowndes, 1917 October (Box 4, Folder 111)
  - Coudert, Frederic R.
    - 1914 Jan, 1915 September - October (Box 4, Folder 112)
    - (*), 1915 November - December (Box 4, Folder 113)
      See also: Post Office Department, box 32, folder 635
    - (*), 1916 January - Mar, May - September (Box 4, Folder 114-116)
    - 1916 October - November (Box 4, Folder 117)
    - (*), 1917 February - December (Box 4, Folder 118-119)
    - (*), 1918 March - November (Box 4, Folder 120)
      See also: Seldon Bacon, box 1, folder 24
  - (*) Council of National Defense, 1917 February - Dec, 1919 Jan, 1920 February (Box 4, Folder 121)
    See also: Labor, box 28, folder 412
  - Cowan, John F.
    See: James G. Freaney, box 6, folder 193
  - Crabites, Pierre, 1918 Feb, April (Box 4, Folder 121)
  - Cramp Ship and Engine Building Company
    See: Shipping, box 34, folder 730
  - Crampton, Henry E., 1916 April - May, 1917 March (Box 4, Folder 121)
  - Crane, Charles Richard, 1920 February - March (Box 4, Folder 121)
  - Crane, Richard
    See: Great Britain, box 26, folder 321
  - Cranford, Frederick L., 1917 December (Box 4, Folder 122)
  - Cravath, Paul Drennan, 1916 March - Apr, 1917 Feb, 1918 Nov, 1919 January (Box 4, Folder 122)
    See also: Richard Ely, box 5, folder 169
  - Cravath and Henderson, 1918 March (Box 4, Folder 122)
  - Crawford, Augusta M., undated (Box 4, Folder 123)
  - Crawford, F. Stuart, 1928 October (Box 4, Folder 123)
  - Crawford, Richard
    - (*), 1916 January - December (Box 4, Folder 124)
      See also: Key Pittman, box 11, folder 401
    - (*), 1917-1918 (Box 4, Folder 125-127)
  - (*) Creel, George, 1916 Oct, 1917 July - August, 1918 January - August (Box 4, Folder 128-129)
  - Crew Levick Company, 1917 October (Box 4, Folder 130)
    See also: David Wallerstein, box 13, folder 467
  - Crist, Harris McCabe, 1917 December (Box 4, Folder 130)
  - Crocker, Frank L., 1917 May (Box 4, Folder 130)
  - Crocker, Stuart M., 1922 November (Box 4, Folder 131)
  - Crocker, William T., 1917 April - May (Box 4, Folder 131)
  - Cromwell, Agnes Whitney (Mrs. Seymour L.), [1916 Mar?] (Box 4, Folder 131)
  - Crosby, Oscar T.
    See: Gordon Auchincloss (1918 Jun 29), box 1, folder 17 See: Russia, box 33, folder 666
  - Crowder, Enoch H., 1917 August - September (Box 4, Folder 132)
    See also: Cuba, box 24, folder 208
  - Crowe, Eyre, 1919 October (Box 4, Folder 132)
  - Crowninshield, Francis Welch, 1941 December (Box 4, Folder 132)
  - Cuba Company
    See: Herbert C. Lakin, box 8, folder 296
  - Cuba Railroad Company
  - Cummings, Homer S., 1920 January - February (Box 4, Folder 132)
  - Cunningham, Philip J., 1918 March (Box 4, Folder 133)
  - Cuozzo, Ernest Joseph, 1917 June (Box 4, Folder 133)
  - Curtis, Charles, 1919 February (Box 4, Folder 133)
  - Curtis, Frazier, 1919 December (Box 4, Folder 133)
  - Curtis, George Milton, Jr., 1919 January (Box 4, Folder 133)
  - Czechoslovak National Council
    See: Tomáš G. Masaryk, box 10, folder 349 See: Charles Pergler, box 11, folder 388
  - Daniels, C. C., 1917 October (Box 4, Folder 134)
  - Daniels, Josephus, 1919 Jul, 1924 June (Box 4, Folder 134)
  - Davidson, M.
    See: Norman Hapgood (1919 Jun 13), box 7, folders 233-238
  - Davies, Joseph E., 1936 November (Box 4, Folder 134)
  - Davis, Gherardi, 1916 Oct, Dec; 1918 November (Box 4, Folder 134)
  - Davis, John William
    - 1919 January - May (Box 4, Folder 135)
      See also: Gordon Auchincloss (1918 Aug 28), box 1, folder 17
    - (*), 1919 June - September (Box 4, Folder 136)
    - 1919 October - 1921 February (Box 4, Folder 137-140)
    - (*), 1923 July - August, 1924 August - Sep, 1925 Jan, undated (Box 4, Folder 141)
  - Davis, Norman H., 1919 May, Jul; 1920 Feb, Aug, Dec; 1921 Mar; 1936 January (Box 4, Folder 142)
    See also: Germany, box 26, folder 309
  - Davis, Robert
    See: Armenia, box 22, folder 115
  - Dawson, Warrington
    See: France, box 25, folder 261
  - Day, George Parmly, 1918 April (Box 4, Folder 143)
  - Day, Sherman, 1918 May (Box 4, Folder 143)
  - Dearing, Fred Morris, 1923 May, 1926 November (Box 4, Folder 144)
  - Deas, Nellie (Mrs. H. L.), 1919 Nov, 1924 July (Box 4, Folder 144)
  - (*) Debevoise, Thomas M., 1916 August - 1917 Apr, 1919 December - 1920 January (Box 4, Folder 144)
  - Dehlgren, Sten
    See: Björkman, Edwin (1919 Mar 10), box 2, folder 54
  - Delafield, John Ross, 1920 March (Box 5, Folder 145)
  - [Delano, William Adams?], 1919 January (Box 5, Folder 145)
  - Delehanty, James A., 1919 September - October (Box 5, Folder 145)
  - Democratic National Committee, 1920 October (Box 5, Folder 145)
  - Denby, Charles, 1918 May (Box 5, Folder 146)
  - Denman, William, 1917 April - December (Box 5, Folder 146)
    See also: Auchincloss, Gordon (1917 Aug 30), box 1, folder 15
  - Dennett, Tyler, 1928 Nov, 1929 March (Box 5, Folder 147)
  - Diocesan Convention of New York, 1913 November (Box 5, Folder 149)
  - (*) Dix, William C., 1919 January - April (Box 5, Folder 149)
  - Dixon, Thomas D., 1920 March - April (Box 5, Folder 149)
  - Dmowski, Roman
    See: Poland, box 32, folder 619
  - Dockweiler, Isidore B., 1917 August (Box 5, Folder 150)
  - Dodge, Cleveland Hoadley, 1916 May - Aug, 1917 May (Box 5, Folder 150)
  - Doheny, Edward Laurence
    See: Gordan Auchincloss (1919 Feb 4), box 1, folders 19-22 See: Mexico, box 30, folder 504
  - Domeratzky, Louis
    See: Finland, box 25, folder 245
  - Dominian, Leon
    See: Latin America, box 28, folder 425
  - Dooling, John T., 1919 April - May (Box 5, Folder 150)
  - Douglas, Charles A., 1916 March - June, 1919 June (Box 5, Folder 151)
  - Dowling-Draper (Box 5, Folder 152)
    - Dowling, Frank L., 1919 April - May (Box 5, Folder 152)
    - Doyle, Michael Francis
      See: Ireland, box 27, folder 370
    - Draper, George, 1919 May (Box 5, Folder 152)
  - Dresel, Ellis Loring
    - (*), 1919 October - 1920 March 8 (Box 5, Folder 153)
      See also: Baltic States, box 23, folder 140
      See also: German Tankers, box 25, folders 267-272
      See also: Poland, box 32, folder 621
      See also: Supreme Economic Council, box 34, folder 769
      See also: Treaty of Versailles, box 35, folder 811
    - 1920 March 16-24, April - Jun; 1922 February (Box 5, Folder 154-155)
  - Droppers, Garrett, 1920 October (Box 5, Folder 156)
  - Drummond, Eric
    See: Peace Efforts, box 32, folder 593
  - DuBois, Arthur W., 1919 October - November (Box 5, Folder 156)
    See also: American Mission, box 22, folder 101
  - DuBose, Mary H., 1918 July (Box 5, Folder 156)
  - Dudley, R. M.
    See: McLemore, Atkins Jefferson, box 10, folder 343
  - Duffy, Matthew, 1939 April (Box 5, Folder 157)
  - Dulles, Allen Welsh, 1919 Oct, December (Box 5, Folder 157)
    See also: Adriatic Question, box 21, folder 31 See also: American Mission, box 3, folder 99 See also: Baltic States, box 23, folder 144 See also: Hungary, box 26, folder 361 See also: Poland, box 32, folder 626 See also: Rumania, box 32, folder 660 See also: Yugoslavia, box 37, folder 863 See also: Yugoslavia, box 37, folder 866
  - (*) Dulles, John Foster, 1916 July - 1917 May, 1919 Aug, 1920 Apr, 1935 June (Box 5, Folder 158)
    See also: American Mission, box 22, folder 99 See also: Germany, box 25, folder 295 See also: Rumania, box 32, folder 643 See also: Rumania, box 32, folder 646 See also: Russia, box 33, folder 679 See also: Yugoslavia, box 37, folder 860
  - Dumba, Constantin Theodor, 1915 September (Box 5, Folder 159)
    See also: Woodrow Wilson (1915 Sep 28), box 14, folders 488-494
  - Dunn, James C.
    See: Dominican Republic, box 24, folder 230
  - Dutasta, P.
    See: Luis Suazo, box 13, folder 451
  - Dyer, Charles B.
    See: Germany, box 25, folder 300
  - Dyer, George R., 1916 October - 1917 June (Box 5, Folder 159)
  - Eastley, Ralph Montgomery, 1916 Jun, 1918 February, 1924 Jul, 1938 February (Box 5, Folder 159)
  - Eastmond, A. H., 1915 December (Box 5, Folder 159)
  - Edwards, Clarence Ransom, 1907 June (Box 5, Folder 160)
  - Edwards, William, 1915 Dec, 1917 September (Box 5, Folder 160)
  - Egan, Eleanor Franklin (Mrs. Martin), 1918 April (Box 5, Folder 160)
  - Egan, Martin
    - 1915 September - 1917 Apr, 1918 March - July (Box 5, Folder 161-162)
    - (*), 1918 August - 1919 Mar, 1920 Jun, 1935 December (Box 5, Folder 163)
  - (*) Egan, Maurice Francis, 1918 Apr, 1919 January - 1920 Dec, 1922 January (Box 5, Folder 164)
  - Eisner, Mark, 1919 February (Box 5, Folder 164)
  - (*) Ekengren, Wilhelm August Ferdinand, 1917 July - 1918 March (Box 5, Folder 165)
  - Eldridge, Dudley G., 1919 February (Box 5, Folder 166)
  - (*) Elkus, Abram I., 1916 Mar, Oct, Dec; 1917 Jan, Jul, November - Dec; 1918 February - Mar, Oct; 1919 February (Box 5, Folder 167-168)
  - Elliman, Douglas L., 1920 May (Box 5, Folder 169)
  - Elliott, Jackson S.
    See: Associated Press, box 1, folder 13
  - Ely, Richard, 1918 December (Box 5, Folder 169)
  - Emery, Frederick Azro
    See: China, box 24, folder 194 See: Japan, box 28, folder 399
  - Engert, Cornelius van H.
    See: Persia, box 32, folder 607
  - Eno, Henry Lane, 1917 November - Dec, 1919 March (Box 5, Folder 169)
  - Equitable Life Assurance Society, 1916 Apr, 1917 Oct, 1919 February (Box 5, Folder 169)
  - Ernst, Oswald Herbert, 1905 Apr, 1918 October - Nov, 1924 February (Box 5, Folder 170)
  - Essary, Jesse Frederick, 1918 March (Box 5, Folder 170)
  - Eustis, Edith L. Morton (Mrs. William Corcoran), 1918 April (Box 5, Folder 171)
  - Evening Mail (New York), 1917 December (Box 5, Folder 171)
  - Ewing, John
    See: John W. Belt, box 2, folder 45
  - Eyre, Lincoln, 1919 Oct, 1920 March (Box 5, Folder 172)
  - Fairchild, G. W., 1917 August (Box 5, Folder 172)
  - Fallows, Edward H.
    See: George W. Wickersham, box 13, folder 484
  - Faramond, ____, 1919 October - November (Box 5, Folder 172)
  - Farrand, Max, 1917 September (Box 5, Folder 172)
  - Faulkner, Charles J., Jr., 1915 Nov, 1917 April - May (Box 5, Folder 173)
  - Fay, [I. W.?], 1918 February (Box 5, Folder 173)
  - Fels, ____ de, [1919 Dec?] (Box 5, Folder 173)
  - Fernández Guardia, Ricardo, 1917 February - March (Box 5, Folder 174)
  - Ferrara, Orestes, 1917 March (Box 5, Folder 174)
    See also: Andujar, Anthony, box 1, folder 10 See also: Martin W. Littleton, box 9, folder 328
  - Ferraris, Maggiorino, 1919 November (Box 5, Folder 174)
  - Fêtes de la Liberté, 1919 Sep, November (Box 5, Folder 175)
  - Field, Walter S., 1916 Nov; 1917 Jun, Aug; 1919 Jan, March (Box 5, Folder 175)
  - Filene, Edward A., 1919 August - September (Box 5, Folder 175)
  - Filley, O. B., 1918 Feb, April (Box 5, Folder 176)
  - Finley, John Huston, 1918 July (Box 5, Folder 176)
  - Fish, Stuyvesant, 1915 September (Box 5, Folder 177)
  - Fisher, Irving
    See: Nipgen, Alvin T., box 10, folder 369
  - Fleming, William Bowyer, 1917 November (Box 5, Folder 177)
  - Fletcher, Duncan Upshaw, 1918 December - 1919 January (Box 5, Folder 177)
  - Fletcher, Henry Prather
    - (*), 1917 February - 1918 March (Box 5, Folder 178)
    - 1918 April - June (Box 5, Folder 179)
    - (*), 1918 July - 1920 Jun, 1923 May, [1928?] March (Box 5, Folder 180-181)
  - Flint, Charles Ranlett, 1917 May - June (Box 6, Folder 182)
  - Flint and Co.
    See: W. Scott Proskey, box 12, folder 409
  - Flood, Henry Delaware, 1917 April, 1918 Feb, April (Box 6, Folder 182)
  - Flournoy, James Campbell, 1918 Aug, 1920 January - February (Box 6, Folder 182)
  - Flynn, William James, 1917 April (Box 6, Folder 183)
  - Fogel, Rube R., 1918 October (Box 6, Folder 183)
  - Ford, Guy Stanton
    See: George Creel (1918 Jan 11), box 4, folders 128-129
  - Fordyce, Samuel W., Jr., 1919 March - Apr, 1924 July (Box 6, Folder 184)
  - Fort, John Franklin, 1918 January (Box 6, Folder 184)
  - (*) Fosdick, Raymond Blaine, 1914 January, 1915 December - 1916 January, 1919 May - 1920 January (Box 6, Folder 185)
    See also: John Foster Dulles (1919 Aug 14), box 5, folder 158 See also: Treaty of Versailles, box 35, folder 810
  - Foster, John Watson, 1916 December - 1917 March (Box 6, Folder 186)
  - Foster, Philip Lawrence, 1917 May (Box 6, Folder 186)
  - Fox, Edward Lyell
    See: Victor D. Herbster, box 7, folder 251
  - Francis, David Rowland, 1916 April - 1917 July, 1919 April - July (Box 6, Folder 187-191)
  - Frankfurter, Felix, 1919 Aug, 1920 June (Box 6, Folder 192)
    See also: France, box 25, folder 253 See also: Labor, box 28, folder 410
  - Franklin, George Small, 1919 April - May (Box 6, Folder 192)
  - Freaney, James G., 1915 December - 1916 January (Box 6, Folder 193)
  - French, Mary N. (Mrs. S. B.), 1916 May (Box 6, Folder 193)
  - Frost, Wesley
    See: Shipping, box 34, folder 740
  - Fuller, Loie, 1926 November - 1927 May (Box 6, Folder 194)
  - Fuller, Paul, Jr., 1917 October - 1918 Jan, 1919 February - March (Box 6, Folder 194)
    See also: Trade, box 35, folder 795
  - Fyfe, Hamilton, 1917 August (Box 6, Folder 195)
  - Gade, John A., 1917 October - Nov, 1942 April (Box 6, Folder 195)
    See also: Norman Hapgood, box 7, folders 233-238, 1919 Nov 2 See also: Baltic States, box 21, folder 145
  - Gale, William Holt, 1917 February (Box 6, Folder 195)
  - Gallauner, Edmund, 1919 January - July (Box 6, Folder 195)
  - (*) Gama, Domicio da, 1916 February - 1918 Oct, 1919 November - 1920 Jul, 1921 March (Box 6, Folder 196)
    See also: Latin America, box 28, folder 420
  - Gardner, Augustus P., 1917 Feb, July (Box 6, Folder 197)
  - Garfield, Harry A., 1918 Dec, 1919 Apr, 1920 March - May (Box 6, Folder 197)
  - Garfield, James R.
    See: Mexico, box 29, folder 487 See: Mexico, box 29, folder 496
  - (*) Garrison, Lindley M., 1916 March - May, 1919 February (Box 6, Folder 198)
  - (*) Garvan, Francis P., 1919 April - June (Box 6, Folder 199)
  - Gary, Hampson, 1918 Feb, 1919 June - October (Box 6, Folder 200)
  - Gaunt, Guy C., 1917 May - June (Box 6, Folder 200)
  - Gavit, John P., 1916 December (Box 6, Folder 201)
  - Gay, Edward J., 1919 March (Box 6, Folder 201)
  - General Electric Company
    See: Stuart M. Crocker, box 4, folder 131
  - Gerard, James W.
    - (*), 1916 February - 1917 July (Box 6, Folder 202)
      See also: George Creel (1918 Feb 7), box 4, folders 128-129
      See also: Edward M. House (1917 July 24), box 8, folder 270
      See also: Peace Efforts, box 32, folder 593
    - (*), 1920 January - May (Box 6, Folder 203-205)
  - Gerry, Mabel, 1919 May (Box 6, Folder 206)
  - Gersdorff, Carl A. de, 1920 June (Box 6, Folder 206)
  - (*) Gibson, Hugh S., 1918 April - 1920 Mar, 1940 September (Box 6, Folder 206)
  - Gilbert, Cass, 1919 July (Box 6, Folder 207)
  - Gilchrist, Huntington, 1928 April (Box 6, Folder 207)
  - (*), Gillet, Charles J., 1918 March - April (Box 6, Folder 207)
  - Gilman, Jane Bowler (Mrs. Roger), 1919 December - 1920 January (Box 6, Folder 207)
  - Glass, Carter, 1916 Aug, 1927 October (Box 6, Folder 208)
  - Gleaves, Albert, 1919 Mar, June (Box 6, Folder 208)
  - Glendinning, Robert, 1918 February - May (Box 6, Folder 208)
  - (*) Glynn, Martin H., 1916 May - Jun, 1919 March (Box 6, Folder 209)
  - Godet, Rose Marie, 1918 March (Box 6, Folder 209)
  - (*) Godson, [William Frederick Holford?], 1918 Jan, 1919 September - October (Box 6, Folder 210)
  - Goldman, Sachs and Co., 1915 Dec, 1916 February (Box 6, Folder 211)
  - Goldsmith, Alan G.
    See: Rumania, box 32, folder 649
  - Gompers, Samuel
    See: Labor, box 28, folder 412
  - Gonzales, William E., 1916 Dec, 1919 January (Box 6, Folder 212)
    See also: Cuba, box 24, folder 214
  - Gonzales, William E., 1919 February, 1919 April - 1920 February (Box 6, Folder 213-214)
  - Goodwin, Clarence N., 1917 January - February (Box 6, Folder 215)
  - Gore, Thomas P., 1919 October (Box 6, Folder 215)
  - Gotthardi, Ruggero, 1919 October (Box 6, Folder 216)
  - Grace (W. R.) and Co.
    See: Latin America, box 28, folder 417
  - Graham, George Scott, 1917 July (Box 6, Folder 216)
  - Granberry, John C.
    See: Eleutherios K. Venizelos, box 13, folder 462
  - Grant, Ida H. (Mrs. Frederick Dent), 1919 July (Box 6, Folder 216)
  - Grasty, Charles H., 1922 March (Box 6, Folder 217)
  - Graves, Ransom F., 1920 March - April (Box 6, Folder 217)
  - Gray, Louis Herbert
    See: American Mission, box 22, folder 101 See: Persia, box 32, folders 603-605